simpleseostuff.com 2015-02-24

# Privacy Policy

**  
Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage as well as every other page on our site where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

* Name   
* Email address 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on new products and services. 

Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Cookies:**

Our website uses "cookies" to track customers who purchase from our web site so we can be credited with a sale. 

**Security:**

Please note that we do not collect any personal, confidential or financial information or any other information from users. The only information we collect is the email address of people who opted into our mailing list, and whether or not the user made a purchase. 

**Contact Information:**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please send an email to contact [@] simpleseostuff . com
